

MOHAMMED SUHAIL

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

M suhail3k@gmail.com

www.suhaill.com



O Dubai, UAE

OBJECTIVE

I am seeking a position within an organization in to utilize my skills and abilities in Software development or Web development. Comes with Bachelor's degree in computer science and have more than 2 year experience in Front end with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP and Java in back end to provide quality support to company's IT team in developing and deploying web-based event.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Zone Delivery Services LLC - Dubai, UAE March 2021 to Present

- Working with PHP Laravel framework and Spring Boot for development of ERP software.
- Built REST APIs in Laravel and Spring Boot that served data to front-end to get the information's.
- Collaborated with a team of software engineers to refactor the code and reduce the service loading time.
- Proficient in OOPs concepts. Ability to quickly learn and apply any new technologies.

Software Engineer - Trainee

Quest Innovative Solutions (P) Ltd - Kerala, India July 2020 to January 2021

- Have successfully written HTML, CSS and JavaScript implemented multiple projects.
- Worked on back end with PHP, MySQL and Laravel framework.
- Research for new ideas and implementing them on projects.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA)

University of Calicut 2017-2020

Higher Secondary (Plus Two)

Board of Kerala 2015-2017

Secondary Education (SSLC)

Board of Kerala 2014-2015

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript React

Bootstrap

Jquery

PHP

Java

Laravel

Spring Boot

MySQL

Git

Photoshop

PERSONAL

Date of birth

05/06/1998

Marital Status

Single

Driving License

Yes

LANGUAGES

English

Malayalam

Hindi

PORTFOLIO

www.suhaill.com